Department of Physical Education and Athletics Records UA046
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Programs and publications, 1912 -- 2013; 1950 -- 1990; UA046.007; 5.5 Linear Feet; 27 Volumes
  - Football, Tufts vs. Bates, 20 September, 1952; UA046.007.072.00005 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. W.P.I., 4 October, 1952; UA046.007.072.00006 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Amherst, 1 November, 1952; UA046.007.072.00007 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Massachusetts, 15 November, 1952; UA046.007.072.00008 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Williams, 24 October, 1953; UA046.007.072.00009 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Trinity, 10 October, 1953; UA046.007.072.00010 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Middlebury, 17 October, 1953; UA046.007.072.00011 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Massachusetts, 13 November, 1954; UA046.007.072.00012 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Trinity, 9 October, 1954; UA046.007.072.00013 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Wesleyan, 2 October, 1954; UA046.007.072.00014 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Rochester, 5 November, 1955; UA046.007.072.00015 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Amherst, 29 October, 1955; UA046.007.072.00016 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Williams, 22 October, 1955; UA046.007.072.00017 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Colby, 15 October, 1955; UA046.007.072.00018 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Bowdoin, 24 September, 1955; UA046.007.072.00019 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Bowdoin, 26 September, 1959; UA046.007.072.00020 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Rochester, 7 November, 1959; UA046.007.072.00021 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Amherst, 31 October, 1959; UA046.007.072.00022 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Williams, 24 October, 1959; UA046.007.072.00023 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Bates, 1 October, 1960; UA046.007.072.00024 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Lafayette, 12 November, 1960; UA046.007.072.00025 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Lehigh, 15 October, 1960; UA046.007.072.00026 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Trinity, 8 October, 1960; UA046.007.072.00027 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Williams, 28 October, 1961; UA046.007.072.00028 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Amherst, 4 November, 1961; UA046.007.072.00029 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Colby, 7 October, 1961; UA046.007.072.00030 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. U.S.C.G.A., 18 November, 1961; UA046.007.072.00031 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Bowdoin, 30 September, 1961; UA046.007.072.00032 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Bates, 22 September, 1962; UA046.007.072.00033 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Northeastern, November, 1962; UA046.007.072.00034 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Trinity, 13 October, 1962; UA046.007.072.00035 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Amherst, 2 November, 1963; UA046.007.072.00036 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Williams, 26 October, 1963; UA046.007.072.00037 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Colby, 5 October, 1963; UA046.007.072.00038 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Bowdoin, 28 September, 1963; UA046.007.072.00039 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Hobart, 14 November, 1964; UA046.007.072.00040 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Northeastern, 7 November, 1964; UA046.007.072.00041 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Ohio Wesleyan, 17 October, 1964; UA046.007.072.00042 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts vs. Trinity, 10 October, 1964; UA046.007.072.00043 (Box 72)
  - Football, Tufts v. Bates, 1911 -- 1980; UA046.007.073.00001 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Bowdoin, 1910 -- 1984; UA046.007.073.00002 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Amherst, 1910 -- 1985; UA046.007.073.00003 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Wesleyan, 1909 -- 1987; UA046.007.073.00004 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Williams, 1909 -- 1990; UA046.007.073.00005 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Wesleyan, 1909 -- 1991; UA046.007.073.00006 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Amherst, 1910 -- 1991; UA046.007.073.00007 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Williams, 1910 -- 1992; UA046.007.073.00008 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Williams, 1910 -- 1994; UA046.007.073.00009 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Trinity, 1910 -- 1995; UA046.007.073.00010 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Trinity, 1910 -- 1997; UA046.007.073.00011 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Amherst, 1910 -- 1997; UA046.007.073.00012 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Hamilton, 1909 -- 1998; UA046.007.073.00013 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Williams, 1910 -- 1998; UA046.007.073.00014 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Bowdoin, 1910 -- 1999; UA046.007.073.00015 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Trinity, 1910 -- 1999; UA046.007.073.00016 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Amherst, 1910 -- 1999; UA046.007.073.00017 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Middlebury, 1911 -- 1999; UA046.007.073.00018 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Wesleyan, 2000 -- 2009; UA046.007.073.00019 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Bates, 2000 -- 2010; UA046.007.073.00020 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Williams, 2000 -- 2010; UA046.007.073.00021 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Colby, 2000 -- 2011; UA046.007.073.00022 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Bowdoin, 2001 -- 2010; UA046.007.073.00023 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Trinity, 2001 -- 2010; UA046.007.073.00024 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Middlebury, 2001 -- 2011; UA046.007.073.00025 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Bates, 2002 -- 2009; UA046.007.073.00026 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Williams, 2002 -- 2010; UA046.007.073.00027 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Trinity, 2003 -- 2010; UA046.007.073.00028 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Middlebury, 2003 -- 2011; UA046.007.073.00029 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Bates, 2004 -- 2010; UA046.007.073.00030 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Middlebury, 2005 -- 2011; UA046.007.073.00031 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Bates, 2006 -- 2011; UA046.007.073.00032 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Colby, 2006 -- 2011; UA046.007.073.00033 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Trinity, 2007 -- 2010; UA046.007.073.00034 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Wesleyan, 2008 -- 2009; UA046.007.073.00035 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Bates, 2008 -- 2009; UA046.007.073.00036 (Box 73)
  - Football, Tufts v. Hamilton, 2009 -- 2010; UA046.007.073.00037 (Box 73)
  - Guides and Brochures, 1999 -- 2000; UA046.007.073.00038 (Box 73)
  - Guides and Brochures, 2000; UA046.007.073.00039 (Box 73)
  - Guides and Brochures, 2000 -- 2001; UA046.007.073.00040 (Box 73)
  - Guides and Brochures, 2001; UA046.007.073.00041 (Box 73)
  - Guides and Brochures, 2001 -- 2002; UA046.007.073.00042 (Box 73)
  - Guides and Brochures, 2002; UA046.007.073.00043 (Box 73)
  - Guides and Brochures, 2002 -- 2003; UA046.007.073.00044 (Box 73)
  - Guides and Brochures, 2003; UA046.007.073.00045 (Box 73)
  - Jumbo Club and Distinguished Achievement Award Publications, 1999 -- 2000; UA046.007.073.00046 (Box 73)
  - Sailing Brochure, UA046.007.073.00047 (Box 73)
  - Sports Schedules, Winter-Spring, 1999 -- 2004; UA046.007.073.00048 (Box 73)
  - "Tufts Sports", 1986-09 -- 1988-12; UA046.007.073.00049 (Box 73)
  - Women's Soccer, Final Four Program, Nov. 18-19, 2000; UA046.007.073.00050 (Box 73)
  - Women's Sports Celebration Commemorative Program, 1995 -- 1996; UA046.007.073.00051 (Box 73)
  - Football guide, 1958 -- 1959; UA046.007.073.00052 (Box 73)
  - Football guide, 1960 -- 1963; UA046.007.073.00053 (Box 73)
  - Winter Schedule and Football Ticket Info, Estate of Brent Jackson, 1963 -- 1964; UA046.007.073.00054 (Box 73)
  - Pocket Schedules, 1952 -- 1986; UA046.007.073.00055 (Box 73)
  - Sports Schedules, 1978 -- 1980; UA046.007.073.00056 (Box 73)
  - Sports Schedules, 1980 -- 1990; UA046.007.073.00057 (Box 73)
  - Sports Schedules, 1990 -- 1998; UA046.007.073.00058 (Box 73)
  - Sports Schedules, 1999 -- 2004; UA046.007.073.00059 (Box 73)
  - Soccer Guides, 1988 -- 1992; UA046.007.073.00060 (Box 73)
  - Women's Field Hockey and Lacrosse brochure, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.007.073.00061 (Box 73)
  - Women's Swimming and Diving Schedule Brochures, 2000 -- 2009; UA046.007.073.00062 (Box 73)
  - Field Hockey Schedule Brochures, 2003 -- 2008; UA046.007.073.00063 (Box 73)
  - Football Schedule Brochures, 2003 -- 2008; UA046.007.073.00064 (Box 73)
  - Women's Soccer Schedule Brochures, 2003 -- 2008; UA046.007.073.00065 (Box 73)
  - Volleyball Schedule Brochures, 2003 -- 2008; UA046.007.073.00066 (Box 73)
  - Women's Basketball Schedule Brochures, 2003 -- 2009; UA046.007.073.00067 (Box 73)
  - Men's Basketball Schedule Brochures, 2003 -- 2009; UA046.007.073.00068 (Box 73)
  - Women's Cross Country/Track and Field Schedule Brochures, 2003 -- 2009; UA046.007.073.00069 (Box 73)
  - Men's Cross Country/Track and Field Schedule Brochures, 2003 -- 2009; UA046.007.073.00070 (Box 73)
  - Hockey Schedule Brochures, 2003 -- 2009; UA046.007.073.00071 (Box 73)
  - Men's Swimming and Diving Schedule Brochures, 2003 -- 2009; UA046.007.073.00072 (Box 73)
  - Men's Lacrosse Schedule, 2004 -- 2008; UA046.007.073.00073 (Box 73)
  - Basketball Schedule Brochures, 2004 -- 2009; UA046.007.073.00074 (Box 73)
  - Women's Lacrosse Schedule Brochures, 2004 -- 2008; UA046.007.073.00075 (Box 73)
  - Men's Tennis Schedule Brochures, 2004 -- 2008; UA046.007.073.00076 (Box 73)
  - Women's Tennis Schedule Brochures, 2004 -- 2009; UA046.007.073.00077 (Box 73)
  - Men's Lacrosse Schedule Brochures, 2005 -- 2008; UA046.007.073.00078 (Box 73)
  - Men's Soccer Schedule Brochures, 2005 -- 2008; UA046.007.073.00079 (Box 73)
  - Softball Schedule Brochures, 2007 -- 2008; UA046.007.073.00080 (Box 73)
  - Men's Squash Schedule Brochure, 2007 -- 2008; UA046.007.073.00081 (Box 73)
  - Women's Squash Schedule Brochure, 2007 -- 2008; UA046.007.073.00082 (Box 73)
  - Tufts University Athletics brochures, 1960 -- 2010; UA046.007.073.00083 (Box 73)
  - Athletics Brochures, 2008 -- 2009; UA046.007.073.00084 (Box 73)
  - Hockey guides, 1989 -- 1996; UA046.007.073.00085 (Box 73)
  - Five Decades of Tufts Athletics, 1950 -- 2000; UA046.007.073.00086 (Box 73)
  - Women of Tufts Calendar, 1986; UA046.007.073.00087 (Box 73)
  - Guides and Brochures includes Jumbo Jottings, 1975 -- 1988; UA046.007.073.00088 (Box 73)
  - Tufts Sports News, 1974; UA046.007.073.00089 (Box 73)
  - Tufts Sports Fall/Winter, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.007.073.00090 (Box 73)
  - Tufts Sports Summer, 1998; UA046.007.073.00091 (Box 73)
  - Tufts Swimming and Diving Women vs. Bates, 2005; UA046.007.073.00092 (Box 73)
  - 50th Anniversary of the 1934 undefeated football, 1984; UA046.007.073.00093 (Box 73)
  - Cavalcade of Champions, 1982; UA046.007.073.00094 (Box 73)
  - Celebrating Jumbo program, 1999; UA046.007.073.00095 (Box 73)
  - Jumbos Football Preview, 1969; UA046.007.073.00096 (Box 73)
  - 1953 Lacrosse 50th Reunion Schedule, 2003; UA046.007.073.00097 (Box 73)
  - Celebrating the Future Tufts Athletic and Fitness Center Beyond Borders Campaign, 2007; UA046.007.073.00098 (Box 73)
  - 60th Anniversary of the 1950 Tufts Baseball Team, 2010; UA046.007.073.00099 (Box 73)
  - All Sports Banquet program, 1967; UA046.007.073.00100 (Box 73)
  - Testimonial to Harry Arlanson, 1966; UA046.007.073.00101 (Box 73)
  - Ground breaking ceremony for the Gantcher Family Sports and Convocation Center, 1998; UA046.007.073.00102 (Box 73)
  - Chase Gymnasium Dedication Program, 1996; UA046.007.073.00103 (Box 73)
  - Senior Awards Dinner, 2001; UA046.007.073.00104 (Box 73)
  - Jumbo Club 32nd Annual Awards Dinner, 2001; UA046.007.073.00105 (Box 73)
  - Football Harvard vs. Tufts, 1956; UA046.007.163.00001 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Rochester, 1959; UA046.007.163.00002 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Bates, 1960; UA046.007.163.00003 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Trinity, 1960; UA046.007.163.00004 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Williams, 1962; UA046.007.163.00005 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Northeastern, 1962; UA046.007.163.00006 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Bowdoin, 1963; UA046.007.163.00007 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Williams, 1963; UA046.007.163.00008 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Colby, 1963; UA046.007.163.00009 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Amherst, 1963; UA046.007.163.00010 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Colby, 1979; UA046.007.163.00011 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. WPI, 1986; UA046.007.163.00012 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Middlebury, 1999; UA046.007.163.00013 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Williams, 2000; UA046.007.163.00014 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Hamilton, 2002; UA046.007.163.00015 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Williams, 2002; UA046.007.163.00016 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Colby, 2002; UA046.007.163.00017 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Bowdoin, 2003; UA046.007.163.00018 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Amherst, 2003; UA046.007.163.00019 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Middlebury, 2003; UA046.007.163.00020 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Williams, 2004; UA046.007.163.00021 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Colby, 2004; UA046.007.163.00022 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Wesleyan, 2004; UA046.007.163.00023 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Bowdoin, 2005; UA046.007.163.00024 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Trinity, 2005; UA046.007.163.00025 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Amherst, 2005; UA046.007.163.00026 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Hamilton, 2006; UA046.007.163.00027 (Box 163)
  - Tufts Football, 2006; UA046.007.163.00028 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Bowdoin, 2007; UA046.007.163.00029 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Middlebury, 2007; UA046.007.163.00030 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Bates, 2008; UA046.007.163.00031 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Williams, 2008; UA046.007.163.00032 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Colby, 2008; UA046.007.163.00033 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Bowdoin, 2009; UA046.007.163.00034 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Middlebury, 2009; UA046.007.163.00035 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Trinity, 2009; UA046.007.163.00036 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Amherst, 2009; UA046.007.163.00037 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Bates, 2010; UA046.007.163.00038 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Williams, 2010; UA046.007.163.00039 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Colby, 2010; UA046.007.163.00040 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Bowdoin, 2011; UA046.007.163.00041 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Trinity, 2011; UA046.007.163.00042 (Box 163)
  - Football Tufts vs. Bates, 2013; UA046.007.163.00043 (Box 163)
  - College football press kit, 1978; UA046.007.163.00044 (Box 163)
  - Women's college basketball press kit, 1986; UA046.007.163.00045 (Box 163)
  - Spalding's official basketball guide, 1934 -- 1935; UA046.007.163.00046 (Box 163)
  - Boston College vs. Holy Cross, 1968; UA046.007.163.00047 (Box 163)
  - Harvard football news Tufts, 1965; UA046.007.163.00048 (Box 163)
  - New England intercollegiate record book, 1974 -- 1975; UA046.007.163.00049 (Box 163)
  - Boston Globe yachting calendar, 1976; UA046.007.163.00050 (Box 163)
  - Boston College hockey basketball, 1977 -- 1978; UA046.007.163.00051 (Box 163)
  - The Olympian, 1973; UA046.007.163.00052 (Box 163)
  - Easern college hockey magazine and Davis cup, 1978 -- 1988; UA046.007.163.00053 (Box 163)
  - National collegiate championships, 1982 -- 1983; UA046.007.163.00054 (Box 163)
  - 10th annual ECAC diviion III basketball tournament, 1982; UA046.007.163.00055 (Box 163)
  - ECAC women's lacrosse tournament, 1985; UA046.007.163.00056 (Box 163)
  - ECAC New England division III men's basketball championships quarterfinals, 1987; UA046.007.163.00057 (Box 163)
  - ECAC women's lacrosse tournament, 1987; UA046.007.163.00058 (Box 163)
  - ECAC Tufts north division finalists hockey, 1987 -- 1988; UA046.007.163.00059 (Box 163)
  - ECAC women's soccer tournament Tufts vs. Trinity, 1989; UA046.007.163.00060 (Box 163)
  - ECAC New England division III women's lacrosse championship game Tufts vs. Amherst, 1995; UA046.007.163.00061 (Box 163)
  - ECAC NewEngland division III women's soccer tournament, 1996; UA046.007.163.00062 (Box 163)
  - Tufts women's soccer ECAC champs, 1996; UA046.007.163.00063 (Box 163)
  - ECAC division III New England women's lacrosse championship, 1998; UA046.007.163.00064 (Box 163)
  - ECAC New England division III women's soccer championship, 1997; UA046.007.163.00065 (Box 163)
  - ECAC division III North volleyball tournament, 1998; UA046.007.163.00066 (Box 163)
  - ECAC New England division III women's lacrosse tournament, 1999; UA046.007.163.00067 (Box 163)
  - ECAC New England division III men's soccer championships first round Bates vs. Tufts, 1999; UA046.007.163.00068 (Box 163)
  - ECAC division III New England women's lacrosse semi-finals and finals, 2001; UA046.007.163.00069 (Box 163)
  - MAIAW field hockey championship, 1981; UA046.007.163.00070 (Box 163)
  - MAIAW championship field hockey, 1982; UA046.007.163.00071 (Box 163)
  - MIT women's volleyball invitational, 1999; UA046.007.163.00072 (Box 163)
  - MIT women's volleyball invitational, 2000; UA046.007.163.00073 (Box 163)
  - NCAA division III soccer quarterfinals Tufts vs. John Hopkins, 1994; UA046.007.163.00074 (Box 163)
  - NCAA division III women's volleyball New England regional, 1996; UA046.007.163.00075 (Box 163)
  - NCAA New England division III women's soccer tournament ssemifinalsand championship, 1998; UA046.007.163.00076 (Box 163)
  - NCAA division III softball championship, 2000; UA046.007.163.00077 (Box 163)
  - NCAA division III women's softball championship, 2000; UA046.007.163.00078 (Box 163)
  - NCAA soccer Tufts vs. Williams College, 2000; UA046.007.163.00079 (Box 163)
  - NCAA division III women's swimming and diving championships, 2001; UA046.007.163.00080 (Box 163)
  - NCAA division III women's swimming and diving championships, 2002; UA046.007.163.00081 (Box 163)
  - NCAA division Iii women's soccer championship, 2005; UA046.007.163.00082 (Box 163)
  - NCAA swimming and diving championships programs, 2005 -- 2011; UA046.007.163.00083 (Box 163)
  - NCAA soccer championship, 2007; UA046.007.163.00084 (Box 163)
  - NCAA division III men's and women's swimming and diving championships, 2007; UA046.007.163.00085 (Box 163)
  - NCAA volleyball championship brochure, 2009; UA046.007.163.00086 (Box 163)
  - NCAA volleyball championship, 2009; UA046.007.163.00087 (Box 163)
  - NCAA lacrosse championships, 2011; UA046.007.163.00088 (Box 163)
  - NECWLA division II championships lacrosse, 1980; UA046.007.163.00089 (Box 163)
  - NESCAC women's soccer tournament quarterfinals, 2000; UA046.007.163.00090 (Box 163)
  - Intercollegiate crew on the Charles, 2001; UA046.007.163.00091 (Box 163)
  - NESCEC men's soccer tournament, 2001; UA046.007.163.00092 (Box 163)
  - NESCAC baseball tournament, 2002; UA046.007.163.00093 (Box 163)
  - NESCAC volleyballchampionship, 2008; UA046.007.163.00094 (Box 163)
  - NIAC women's basketball tournament, 1980; UA046.007.163.00095 (Box 163)
  - NIAC basketball tournament womens, 1981; UA046.007.163.00096 (Box 163)
  - NIAC volleyball championship, 1984; UA046.007.163.00097 (Box 163)
  - NIAC women's soccer championship, 1985; UA046.007.163.00098 (Box 163)
  - NIAC women's soccer tournament, 1988; UA046.007.163.00099 (Box 163)
  - Volleyball UNH wildcat classic, 1981; UA046.007.163.00100 (Box 163)
  - Pomona-Pitzer volleyball invitational tournament, 1997; UA046.007.163.00101 (Box 163)
  - Tufts women's basketball tournament, 1982; UA046.007.163.00102 (Box 163)
  - New England college women's lacrosse tournament, 1982; UA046.007.163.00103 (Box 163)
  - Tufts University fourth annual invitational basketball tournament, 1989; UA046.007.163.00104 (Box 163)
  - Babson College women's basketball invitational tournament, 1990; UA046.007.163.00105 (Box 163)
  - Tufts University fall rowing open housse and regatta spectator's guide, 1999; UA046.007.163.00106 (Box 163)
- Constitution for Government of Athletics and meeting minutes, 1908 -- 1948; UA046.008; 1 Volumes
  This series contains a small book containing the constitution for the government of athletics in Tufts College as well as minutes for meetings.
  This series contains one item.
  - Constitution for the government of athletics in Tufts College, 1908 -- 1948; UA046.008.001.001 (Box 1)
- Ephemera, 1876 -- 2012; 1944 -- 1992; UA046.009; 17.55 Linear Feet; 2 Artifact(s)
  This series contains ephemera, which includes ribbons, plaques, and T-shirts of the Department of Athletics.
  This series is arranged as found.
  - Plaque saluting 1927 undefeated football team, 1977; UA046.009.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Plaque of original sketch of Captain's Gate at Ellis Oval, 1992; UA046.009.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Richard Roy Phillips' medals, 1940 -- 1943; UA046.009.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Three Tufts booster pins, 1980; UA046.009.001.00004 (Box 1)
    These items were found uncatalogued in the stacks in Winter 2009. Rocky Carzo indicated that they were used as a booster club item to help support Tufts Athletics. The pins were sold by Mr. and Mrs. Frank Del Vecchio, a local couple who sold items such as pins, pennants, and balloons to support the Tufts football team and their family. If more information is desired concerning the Del Vecchio family there are a number of articles in the Medford newspaper. There are three pins in this box.
  - Letter award sweaters, football, 1931; UA046.009.002 (Box 2)
    Two sweaters donated by Mr. Edward A. Jackman 31 in 1979, one belonging to him and the other belonging to an unknown football player from the same time period.
  - Jumbo Stampede T-shirts, Sixth and Eighth Annual, UA046.009.003 (Box 3)
  - Althletic Association varsity letter certificate, 1947; UA046.009.004.00001 (Box 4)
    Donated by Edward M. Lee; certificate for Varsity Letter in Baseball.
  - Personal trophy collection of George Walter Rowbotham E'97, 1890 -- 1897; UA046.009.005 (Box 5)
    Items are extremely delicate. DO NOT ADD to this box. These ribbons and medals were found uncatalogued in the stacks in the winter of 2009. The ribbons represent trophies won by George Walter Rowbotham in field day events while attending Tufts College. Originally these items were pinned to a velvet screen and framed with a plaque. Due to the delicate nature of the materials the items have been removed from their original housing and wrapped in unbuffered paper. Included in this box is a plaque which reads " Personal trophy collection of George Walter Rowbotham E'97June 17, 1874-August 18, 1968 presented to Tufts by his widow October, 11, 1968. Additionally there are three medals dated 1890, presumably from Mr. Rowbotham's high school career. For more information on George Walter Rowbotham please see his vertical file.
  - Williams vs. Tufts Football Homecoming Ticket., 1910 -- 1973; UA046.009.006.00001 (Box 4)
  - Charles Hingston Memorial Award, 1966 -- 1976; UA046.009.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Baseball: Tufts vs. Harvard, plaque, 1900; UA046.009.007.00002 (Box 7)
    Base Ball Holmes' Field, April 20, 1895 Tufts 11 - Harvard 7 Holmes' Field, April 9, 1899 Tufts 7 - Harvard 3 Soldiers' Field, May 17, 1899 Tufts 10 - Harvard 4
  - Championship baseball bat won by the Class of 1887, 1886; UA046.009.007.00003 (Box 6)
  - Field Hockey Skirt, 1950 -- 2000; UA046.009.184.00001 (Box 184)
    Brown, teal and green wrap skirt with one button at waist. Lableld #50.
  - Tufts Baseball Jersey, 1922; UA046.009.184.00002 (Box 184)
    Brown wool jersey with rust colored "Tufts" across front of shirt. Front closure top half of shirt, white buttons.
  - Maroon Blazer, 1941; UA046.009.184.00003 (Box 184)
    Maroon blazer with Tufts crest on front left breast pocket in white embroidery and "41"
  - Gray Blazer, 1942; UA046.009.184.00004 (Box 184)
    Gray blazer with Tufts crest on front left breast pocket in blue embrpidery, "42"
  - Track Letter Jacket, 1980; UA046.009.184.00005 (Box 184)
    Royal blue track letter jacket, wool, White circular patch with blue embroidery on front left breast pocket area, "Indoor Track NE Div. III Champs 11-0" on patch